At his previous school he had no equal.
Euigyeom has always... been the best.
Clear.
The deputy director is very
praised Uigeom's performance.
He even received a gold medal
at the International Olympiad.
And he has many awards from various competitions.
Deputy Director specially
asked you to pay attention to this.
And we too... it’s very nice when you come to us
such a capable student is transferred.
Eugyom.
This school is different from Seomun.
Everything will be different here.
After all, different students study here.
Different atmosphere.
You understand?
Eugyeom won't have any problems.
Nothing comes amiss to him.
Am I right?
Yes.
So, everything is in place.
So.
We have a new student in our class.
Kang Yoongi!
And you're early today.
Yes, teacher.
There were no traffic jams in the metro.
Wow! There were no traffic jams in the subway?
Stop being late, okay?
Yes.
Yes, Kim Eugyeom.
Maybe you could introduce yourself?
I'm Kim Eugyeom.
Is that all?
Brevity is the sister of talent, right?
Yes!
There's a place back there, sit down there.
Now let's discuss your career plan.
Well? What? What?
Fill out the form before tomorrow
morning lineup. Agreed?
Yes.
Kim Eugyeom...
was the best student... at Somun school.
Make friends with him
and help in school life.
Yes!
Don't bully or mock him.
- Choi Hongil!
- What?
Did you hear?
Yes.
Why the best student
Has Somun transferred to us?
To our school.
Don't you dare sleep in class.
Yeah.
And don’t do nonsense, understand?
Yes.
Free!
What kind of idiot?
Ignores?
He just transferred.
Leave him alone, you idiot.
Don't touch the best student.
Taechhi Station Stop
Next stop: Hagyeul.
So, let's look at problem number seven.
For all real X
x cubed + ax squared - 3x + 1 equals
x - 1, x squared + dx + c.
I'm home.
Oh, back already?
How do you like the new school?
Fine.
This shape is more beautiful.
Do you want anything?
Mom.
Can I try... your pills?
For what?
Why does a high school student need pills?
Forget.
Back?
What page?
178th.
I drank a little today.
All these doctors...
so disgusting.
They require attention.
They think they are the best.
Kim Eugyom.
Focus.
I'm sorry.
Why these apologies?
Again.
Another mistake.
Like this.
You can, after all.
Why are you always wrong here?
Focus, okay?
Further.
Jerk!
What a freak.
I told you to buy a bun
and put it on the table or not?
Come here.
Minsop.
You haven't been beaten for a couple of days.
Already bolder, I see?
Get up, idiot.
I told you to buy a bun.
I'm dying of hunger.
Did you have breakfast?
Yes, I ate.
Hongil... I'm sorry.
Did your mom feed you this morning?
Well cool.
And I'm dying of hunger.
Hey.
Any money?
- Two pieces?
- Two thousand won.
Really?
Should I drag you in?
I have no strength at all on an empty stomach.
You will carry me all day.
Did they give you this at school?
For what?
Haven't you written your plans yet?
What a dead guy.
It's time for you to pump your legs.
Get up already, idiot.
Eeyore!
- Hey, come on.
- So, let's go!
- And-go-go, and-go-go, and-go-go!
- Look, what an ass!
Ride faster.
Horse number one!
Why so dead, moron?
You had breakfast.
Crap! Minsop.
Why are you such a weak slug?
Hey.
You said you had breakfast.
Why are you such a weakling?
Nonentity.
Rise.
What did you do yesterday?
Did you watch porn?
No, I didn't look.
“No, I didn’t look.”
Then why are you so lethargic, huh?
I played a hundred pounds yesterday!
I heard you yesterday
Had a great dinner, huh?
Am I wrong?
Damn.
Hey!
Is that you to me?
Are you crazy?
Barked at me?!
Did you raise your voice?
Are you a puppy?!
How dare you, you pathetic piece of shit?!
Is the damn nerd yelling at me?
Who are you thinking of shouting at, huh?
Nice one, Hongil!
The teacher will come right now.
Yes, I just can’t believe my ears.
Oh, I'm impressed.
Get up already, puppy.
Good already.
I won't touch him.
Bro, relax.
You are now blacklisted.
Get to your desk.
Got up quickly!
Do you want more?
What have you hatched, idiots?
And this moron suddenly screamed.
My mind was completely blown away.
“What is this? Am I dreaming?"
Was he completely confused, or what?
Here comes the psycho.
Exactly.
Hey!
Come here, nerd!
Excuse me.
- I just...
- Yes, yes, I understand.
Your mind went crazy in that moment.
But it's okay, I'll fix it.
Drive away the money.
What?
There is a price to pay for bad behavior.
My mood is ruined.
Because of you.
Wow.
A sea of ​​money.
Are you a major?
Am I right?
Here are ten pieces.
Why does he need ten grand?
Take out your mobile phone.
For what?
Don't be afraid. Am I a gopnik?
I'll write down my number.
Well, tell me the password, puppy.
I don't have one.
Is it true?
"Brother Hongil."
You must answer me in ten seconds.
OK.
But when I'm at the academy
or I'm studying at home, I won't be able to watch...
You will receive for every second.
Go.
What, karaoke?
I don't see any fear in him.
Yes, he is pissing from fear.
Didn't you see how he was shaking?
Didn't notice?
And you?
The academy called.
If you fail the exam,
you will be transferred to the middle group.
I promised them that this wouldn't happen.
Uygyom, your headphones...
Hey puppy!
Are you kidding?
I ordered you to buy me a bun!
Tired of living?
Sorry.
I forgot.
You need to forget about something else.
Did you have breakfast?
Yes.
Did your mother feed you delicious food?
Do you dare sit with headphones on?
when an elder stands in front of you?
What?
Where is the sound?
Is this from Guardians of the Galaxy?
How to enable it?
Give it here.
What?
Play?
Doesn't play.
What is this, huh?
Cool stuff.
Choi Hongil!
What?
Give it back.
Are you crazy?
This is an important thing for me.
Give it back.
Don't want.
Now he's mine.
Hey!
Please...
Give it back.
What a nightmare.
If he is so important to you,
should have been said earlier.
Relax, puppy.
You're scaring me.
Take it.
Hey!
I told you this is important.
And what?
So what now?
What to do?
A? What to do?
Hey!
A simpler face.
Are you mad?
Are you really tired of living?
You're a fucking nerd.
Hongil!
Are you okay?
This puppy, eh!
Damn you.
Suddenly.
Fight!
Hey, close the door!
I'll see you right now...
I'll bury it underground.
Let's.
Try.
Oh, damn!
Let's! Let's!
Scum!
My hair!
Okay, sorry!
Shall we stop them?
What a psycho!
Don't interfere, it's their business.
Who are you?
I?
Judge.
I said that he is important to me.
Why did you do this?
Get off.
Will you answer me for this?
Hey freak!
Wow.
Nice.
Kim Eugyeom!
Hey Kim Eugyeom.
Hey, hey!
I'm Kang Yoongi, we're in the same class.
You fight great. Did you play sports?
I didn't study.
Yes, the ability to fight is a talent.
What will you surprise us with tomorrow?
What are you talking about?
How will you fight?
Why should I fight?
Something tells me that I will have to.
You beat up Choi Hong-il
his friends won't forget this.
I won't fight.
How naive.
Let's see.
Wait and see.
Good luck, Kim Eugyeom!
Eigyom, you are very late,
The exam has already started.
Sorry. I'll try to make it in time.
Let's.
Don't rush to decide.
Thank you.
Back?
I'm home.
- Go wash yourself...
- Kim Eugyeom!
Why were you late for the academy?
I fell asleep on the bus.
You know that if you do poorly,
will you be transferred to the middle group?
Yes.
Expensive?
I'm talking.
Wash yourself and study.
I'll be there soon.
Yes.
Brother.
Listen.
How do you like it?
Cool, right?
Here it is.
Real music.
Brother.
Eugyom.
Don't listen with your ears
but with the heart.
Feel with your heart.
Even though it's not music.
Vibration.
Vibration of life.
Brother.
Why are you up?
What page?
Page 193.
Did you get enough sleep yesterday? A?
And because of you, you moron, I
and I didn’t close my eyes yesterday.
Sorry about yesterday.
What?
Yes, you're definitely a goner.
"Sorry"?
Yes.
I'm really sorry.
Damn, you idiot.
See you later.
What are we going to do?
What should I do?
Let's teach him a lesson.
I didn't expect him to grab my hair.
My father is bald
he is very sensitive to this.
I told you it would start today.
Perhaps Kim Seung Joon will come.
Guy in a hat.
He did boxing and was kind of cool.
But this is not true at all.
If a fight breaks out
and you catch a blow - you're finished.
Get close and take him down.
According to my observations, you are stronger.
Can you leave me alone?
And one more thing...
I really don't fight.
Do you think you have a choice?
He doesn't catch up at all.
Hey, everyone out!
Get out!
Get out.
Get up.
Quickly, quickly!
Fast! Shoo!
Who are you?
Won't you get off?
I? Observer.
Are you kidding?
Yesterday was a lot of fun.
How's your jaw?
When it hit you, you just collapsed.
Choi Hongil, you're an idiot.
Your name is called.
Because you do all sorts of crazy things,
Scum like him gets you.
"Garbage"? Kind of rude.
Kill you?
Not.
Hey.
What have I done to you?
Weren't you the one who beat up Hongil?
I already apologized for yesterday, and...
he started it first...
Do you think I'm joking?
On your knees.
Why?
Last chance.
On your knees.
If I get caught smoking, you're screwed.
What are you doing here?
A?
What?
Kim Eugyeom?
He's bleeding.
Kim Seungjoon.
What's your job?
Why are you mocking Eugyeom?
who does nothing but study?
Look at him.
- On the way out. Hey Kang Yoongi.
- Yes.
Take Eugyeom to the infirmary.
Yes.
Let's go, Eugyeom.
Kim Seungjoon.
Are you a bandit?
Mafioso, huh?
Learned to fight and
Are you giving up now?
Only bandits do this.
You hit him.
How can you beat someone
who just transferred to us?
You're a dumbass.
Still don't communicate with your mother?
Do you even know where she is?
What does it matter?
What is the meaning?
Look at him.
Former athlete...
manners
must be
in first place.
Did you want to punch him?
Seriously wanted to hit Kim Seung Joon?
I told you that in such
position you can't do anything.
Definitely necessary
get closer and knock him down.
Did you want to pull him in with your fist?
You would be crushed into dust.
If you learn a little from me,
then you will fight well.
I don't fight at all.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
But he is fighting.
Please.
Don't talk to me.
Hello?
What?
Lost your cassette?
Did you take it?
I returned from the class teacher,
no cassette?
Choi Hongil.
- Where are you?
- So uninteresting.
Rich nerd,
whom the teacher adores.
I ask where are you?
Hey.
Come where we met.
Dumb nerd.
Kim Eugyeom!
Wait!
Hey Kim Eugyeom.
What are you doing?
Don't run.
Save your strength, otherwise they will smear you.
If you hit him,
then he'll go completely crazy, right?
Yes, his eyes are literally bloodshot.
He's crazy, I answer.
Grabs your hair
then he strangles.
He can even bite in with his teeth.
Beware.
Aw! Crap.
I'm going home
but for some reason our paths coincide.
This cassette...
so important to you?
She's a brother.
Brother?
And I need to take care of her.
So you have a brother.
This is understandable. Who has
brothers, they are always strong in spirit.
Because they have been beaten since childhood.
That's why you are so resilient and strong.
Now it's clear.
I've arrived.
Kang Yoongi!
Hello!
Wait a little.
I'll finish with Uygyom,
Then I’ll teach you a lesson too.
Yes, sorry.
I hope we get along.
How he infuriates me.
Go and get it.
Until I broke it.
Hold it.
Don't kill him.
Give me my player.
Did I say no?
I'll give it back.
If you defeat me in battle.
It's simple.
Why should we fight?
- Take off your backpack.
- I said...
I'm not in the mood today.
Enough.
So it’s baked.
Enough!
What a psycho.
Wow.
Do you like hitting people?
Are you really going to fight?
Hey Kim Seungjoon.
You were the first to start all this.
And you took my player!
Damn, what have I done to you?!
What have you done to us?
There was no need to show off.
Get up.
Just let us beat you up, you fucking psycho.
Oh shit.
Are you putting up protection?
Puppy.
He...
Persistent.
Come on.
Like this.
Again.
Slowly?
We need to do it faster.
More.
What's wrong?
Too far?
Funny guy.
More.
Right now.
Then I'll cheat.
Ready.